Mr.
Tommy
Once or no, I can't wait, perlu, limited to the self-size
See you next time.
And you're also being rude.
Sorry, it's long!
Damn it.
Just five more centimeters.
You can reach that.
Jump higher.
Reach it.
Off his foot!
Shuyo Hidaka demonstrates formidable balance and skill.
Karasuno narrowly manages to stop Inazaki from scoring a breakpoint.
Damn it.
Don't get exhausted now.
Complaint, dumbass!
Complaint about what?
Give me one more!
I honestly thought nothing really scared Kageyama anymore.
But it's not only the people across enemy lines that can push you all the way to your limit.
I'm impressed, Hinata.
And Inazaki quickly takes back possession of service.
I'm astounded that they have the guts to go straight from the middle whenever they're in trouble.
And that goes for both teams.
There are times when Natsuma's concentration just sort of snaps suddenly.
But today, for some reason, it actually feels like it keeps getting sharper and sharper.
But I do think there are some actual monsters out there.
Yeah, I'd agree there are at least a few real ones.
True monsters who love playing volleyball day in and day out.
And I get to meet them, stand on the same court with them, to face them head on.
Look at me.
I'm a human being with an invitation to go to the Monster's Ball.
I'm a lucky guy.
The only way to go forward is through this team!
Yeah!
Atsumumiya is serving.
He'd been amusing himself by battling it out with Nishinoya.
But there's no telling who he'll bear his fangs at next.
I can't even imagine the pressure the Karasuno receivers are feeling right now.
Right on the heels of Karasuno's Kageyama, Inanazaki's Atsumumiya pulls off an ace of his own.
An exchange of high-level serves that makes it hard to believe this is a high school game.
It's an unending cycle of hope followed by despair.
Dude.
The ball's in your face before you even know it!
And once again, Inanazaki is at match point.
Guys, we don't need any miracles.
Go, go, let's go, Inanai!
This is how all of our matches go!
Inanai!
Go, go, let's go, Inanai!
Karasuno's down match point and they're still not scared?
I mean, Atsumumiya's serving and they're hanging on by the skin of their teeth.
Let's go, Inanai!
If they push us one step back, we'll go over the edge.
I will never get used to this.
I think my hands and knees are shaking.
But we're not looking for a miracle here.
We're going to do what we've done time and time again and we'll survive like we always do.
A roar out of the silence!
After that graceful jump flow serve, he shakes up Karasuno with an intense spike serve!
It's going over the net!
I'm not going to lose!
Give me one more!
I refuse to lose to him!
This is bad.
Shouyo Hirata runs right down the center!
The ball was about to go over the net, but Tobio Kageyama sets it even higher!
Hidey-ho!
That was up there!
It's like young Hinata has wings!
And the set, I can't believe the ball got to him!
Ha!
Hmm?
What's up?
It's not because he believes in the setter.
Thank you!
Great job, Hinata!
He just knows.
He knows that the ball will come to it.
I thought they had a good chance!
He just assumes they'll get him the ball!
You have my condolences, Kageyama.
That is one terrifying partner you've got there.
And what's so weird about that?
Hala, you need to stop and think some more about other people's feelings!
Huh.
That's funny.
From a heartless bastard like you.
I was not making a joke!
Huh?
I win.
Hey, what?
Stop looking at me like that!
I'm the one who scored the point!
What's your deal?
It's thanks to me you got that.
Nice kill.
Don't say it with that look on your face!
Make it count!
Good, good, good!
Their number 10 is finally in the back row!
Two more rotations until Asahi serves.
That's probably going to be our best bet.
Don't let them get any break points before then!
Man, I'm tired.
Tired of running at full speed.
Tired of jumping.
Tired of their stupid, unpredictable setter.
Samu, front!
If I could just stuff him right now and end it, I'm sure the whole team would lose their minds.
But, I can't do that.
So, you better be there.
Oh, middle blocker Hidata gets the ball back in the air!
Excellent positioning, I'd say.
Go, Hidata!
Ah, dang it.
I thought I already knew this, but...
Wow.
He is an incredible blocker!
Please, God, or Buddha, or Goddess, or...
Or whatever!
Just please, let us have this one point.
Counter!
Back minus!
Nice receive!
Holy cow!
How did he manage to get anywhere close to that?
That play, that guy, is so amazing!
The receive was awesome, sure.
But he was able to get that ball because he's working with the blockers.
All the spikers on the court want to beat out every block and every reception.
The setters want to give the spiker the best advantage possible.
The servers want to attack hard enough that the setter doesn't have to do anything.
They all work together until the ball hits the ground.
If you lose your train of thought for even a second, you get left behind.
Damn it!
My mind is clear, but my legs can't keep up.
Shit, sorry.
Karasuno can barely keep standing.
Kageyama!
You've got this.
Asahi!
Now!
It's perfect.
The first and second years will get to keep hitting these sets.
And so will the new players.
I'm kind of jealous.
Three blockers!
But I also feel a little sorry for them.
Damn it.
Quick, quick, you're Capacito!
Heck yeah!
Nice kill!
That pisses me off.
Wait, what?
What does?
You see him shift the timing on that spike?
He was experimenting with that at our practice match, remember?
Wait, he was?
He waits for the blockers to start falling before he hits.
If he messes that up, it would end up being a weak-ass spike.
I've never noticed that before.
He probably hasn't even mastered it yet, but he made it work there.
And towards the end of the game, when everyone is exhausted, somehow he maintains perfect form in the air.
Man, that guy pissed me off.
And now it's Karasuno's turn to try and end this game!
I think I'm starting to get chest pains from all this stress.
Hmm.
So, the guys out on the court, how do you think they're feeling right about now?
Ugh.
Well, I bet they're all just running on fumes at this point.
And they're also probably fighting off a serious amount of pressure and nervous jitters.
Hmph.
They're also thinking, whoever scores here will be a hero.
Just one more point.
Come on.
Come on!
Does he have to get so giddy over every single thing these first years do?
Number one high school setter, my ass.
Man, I'm so spoiled.
The pressure of the guy demanding the ball?
The murderous rage of a guy who's determined to kill the ball?
It's the best!
And I get to use it all as a decoy.
It doesn't get any better than that.
I'm not gonna let them stop me here.
They don't get to push back my attacks.
They're my attacks, but okay, sure.
Let's put it away.
And Tsuna makes the point.
And Narazaki's attackers have Karasuno's defense at their mercy field.
The Mia twins haven't actually landed their quicks very often during the match we've seen today.
But they still have an impact whenever they fake them effectively.
I'm fairly certain Natsuma was quite eager to keep playing with the new toy he's found.
But he's showing some nice restraint.
I hear the game on court A is intense.
It's the last set and they might hit 30.
30 points?
I would die.
And Narazaki gets this one up too!
Sabu!
Their blockers are stubbornly persistent.
Their nerves must be so frayed that the smallest thing can cause them to snap.
But they are not going to let that happen.
The concentration on both sides is simply tremendous.
Look at that high spike from Ananogiro.
Yeah!
And the crowd goes wild!
That spike went right over the block!
And Narazaki has grabbed Karasuno's tail and they refuse to let go.
Osamumi is in the back, so there won't be a quick.
We've got to use this chance to score.
It's long!
But that punk's going to get the ball in the air.
Gotcha!
I do not believe it!
The audacity of first-year Tobio Kageyama!
Hmm.
Seems as though every Karasano player has been on the offense of this entire game!
They are certainly very focused on the attack, and while that is the source of Karasano's strength, I imagine it consumes a lot of physical and mental energy.
One more point...
Just one more...
It's not gonna make it!
Up front!
Son of a bitch! He's been going for that soft serve the whole time!
It's you!
Back, back!
Chance ball!
Attack!
Hurry!
We have to be faster than them!
Before the enemy gets back on their feet!
Before they catch up!
Wow, that was fast!
Karasano goes in for the kill!
But the leave it on Akagi saves it!
Slower guy, slow the game down!
Left enemy, slow it down!
A line shot!
Don't let it through!
Left!
They're already blocking!
My approach was too short!
I'll rebound it!
Come on! One more time!
Karasano!
Take it easy! Slow it down!
Their determination to score that point right this minute is speeding up their rhythm.
Speed can be a bad influence!
It narrows your view and shortens your breath!
It does make it harder for the other team, but at the same time, you're still struggling yourselves!
Back to the net! Now, do it!
That's mine!
Bowman!
The last one-
…
That's exactly what you do for the이었.
The last one-
Huh.
Try taking it easy.
It's such a simple little thing.
It's easy, but it's also easy to forget.
A high, slow first contact.
A first contact that gives your teammates time to breathe.
What the heck happened to Hinata at that first year's training camp?
The crowd, and even most of the players watching won't think that was a big deal.
They'll think it was just a pass.
I may be small, but I've got talent!
Hey, I wanna hit too!
Throw me a bone here, Kageyama!
Exactly! Spikes are my favorite thing to do!
But it's better than not playing at all, right?
I want to stay on the court the longest.
Oh man.
I think I'm gonna cry.
Significant approach distance achieved!
Synchronize attack!
Making time for your teammates.
Gives time to the other side too.
But that's fine.
Go.
Take them head on!
The final point!
This is it.
Finish it!
It doesn't matter!
Where you hit it from!
We won't let it through that easy!
Check him out!
Yo-oh!
Oh, man! Holy crap!
Upfront! Upfront!
Karasuno's tenacity is throwing an Anasaki into...
Go back! Go back! Go back! Hurry!
Hurry!
Quick! Minus tempo! Back!
This position!
This timing!
This angle!
It's perfection!
To-
To
I think everyone else was surprised.
But not us.
In a battle that lasted a tenth of a second,
when the twins pulled out that fast back row attack,
our two bozos were the only ones who weren't phased in the slightest.
Speed is a very, very strong weapon.
It's mesmerizing.
It makes you look cool.
It feels great.
But it's not invincible.
And they know that.
They know it better than everyone else.
確かなことはいつか
分かる時が来るから
間違ったっていいさ
今想いを止めないで
現実が飛んじゃうような
夢が欲しかったのに
通じつまを合わすだけの日々は
味気ない
何にも怖くなんて泣いて
強がって馬鹿の少年が
今もまだ汗ばむ背中を見つめてるから
奇跡はもういらない
どこまでだって
行ける僕らは
ファンデ
夢も叶うさ
ここまでやってきたのは
偶然なんかじゃなくて
去ってしまう舞台に
だっていたいと
いつでも
強く願い続けた
君がそこにいたから
次回は
プロミスランド
ディング